Hardworking system/network administrator proficient in hardware, software and security planning. Able to select, install, configure and manage components. Highly motivated and currently working towards next big dream ahead - to be successful in Security Research / Penetration Testing field. Acquired number of certifications and courses toward that goal including OSCP certification.

Work History

2017-08 -Current

System Administrator

EFbet Galicia LTD, Sofiq, Bulgaria

- Led server infrastructure development, quality assurance, staging and production systems.
- Implemented, developed and tested installation and update of file servers, print servers and application servers in all departments.
- Installed and upgraded Casino internal and third party software.
- Resolved issues and escalated problems with knowledgeable support and quality service.
- Standardized job tasks and trained junior team members on industry best practices and standards.
- Completed reports detailing network and systems performance, costs and downtime issues.
- Comprehensively maintained stability of essential data backups on daily basis.
- Configured hardware, devices and software to set up work stations for employees.
- Patched software and installed new versions to eliminate security problems and protect data.
- Troubleshoot and diagnosed problems to accurately resolve wide range of technical issues.

2017-01 -2017-07

Temporary Worker

Hardware Services LTD, Swindon, United Kingdom

- Refurbishment of network equipment
- Testing and logging diagnostics data of switches, routers and other network devices.
- Configuration of network devices and servers

Kiril Stefanov

System
Administrator / Ethical
Hacker

Contact

Address

Manastirska 42B Sofia, 1111

Phone

- +359885527554
- +447405319930

E-mail

kiril_stefanov@outlook.com

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/kiril-stefanov-01b27118

Skills

Hardware knowledge

Very Good

Troubleshooting

Very Good

Servers expertise

Very Good

Data security

Very Good

Skill development

Excellent

2006-12 - Service Technician of POS Equipment

Bozhkilov MIT Ltd, Blagoevgrad, Bulgaria

- Completed partial or full dismantling of equipment to quickly repair or replace defective components and restore functionality.
- Conducted diagnostic procedures to determine root cause of customer problems and provide accurate repair recommendations.
- Maintained inventory of repair supplies and ordered parts as needed.
- Accurately and efficiently installed equipment, including Cash registers and POS equipment.
- Established, repaired and optimized networks by installing wiring, cabling and devices.
- Troubleshoot and maintained all networking devices and infrastructure across enterprise including switches, routers and firewalls.
- Administered, supported and monitored databases by proactively resolving database issues and maintaining servers.
- Collaborated with developers and product owners to stay current on product features and intended functionality.
- Walked clients and internal staff through troubleshooting steps to resolve common software issues.
- Operated power drills, wire strippers, pliers and wire connectors to properly install and repair electronic equipment.

Education

2002-09 - Secondary Education: Accelerated English Learning

VIII SOU "Arseni Kostencev" - Blagoevgrad

1994-06 - **Primary Education**

2002-06 VIII SOU "Arseni Kostencev" - Blagoevgrad

Certifications

Network development and administration

Good

Encryption

Very Good

Languages

English

Superior

2019-12

Queues/key-value stores: RabbitMQ, etcd, consul

Web Servers/Reverse proxies: Apache HTTPD, Nginx

Web Hosting Panels: cPanel/WHM CMS: Wordpress, Joomla, Drupal Virtualization: KVM, Virtualbox

Skills and technologies

Security related:

• - Tools and methodologies regarding the different phases of pentesting:

Reconnaissance:

- Nmap
- OpenVAS
- Dirbuster/gobuster
- Metasploit
- Sublist3r
- Amass
- Masscan
- Burp Suite

Threat Modeling & Vulnerability Identification

- Searchsploit/exploit-db
- Metasploit
- Nmap
- MITRE CVE

Exploitation

- Modification of already present scripts/PoCs
- Metasploit
- Impacket
- John The Ripper/Hashcat
- SQLMap
- Burp Suite

Post-Exploitation

- Impacket
- John The Ripper/Hashcat
- Empire
- Metasploit
- Different PowerShell/Bash/Python scripts for gathering system information/versions

Reporting

Cherry Tree

Additional Information

Have personal letter of recommendation from all previous positions